# **Eugenia Zanarini**

# Senior Reference Data Analyst

Front End Developer | Sound Designer

I have experience working in different linguistic and cultural contexts, and I enjoy learning new languages and technologies. I am a problem solver, an effective communicator, and a team player, and I strive to deliver high-quality results in every project I undertake.

# **Experience**

## May 2023 - Present

#### Senior Reference Data Analyst ICE

Spanish role at ICE (Intercontinental Exchange). Updating and sourcing data related to secondary market securities by conducting research through available resources, as well as directly contacting clients. Keeping track of updates through Excel, collaborating as a team to reach goals and fulfil tasks, attend cross trainings, creating training documentation to share with the team.

## October 2023 - April 2024

## Course Administrator, Lecturer Pulse College

Role for the Part-Time Diploma in Audio and Music Technology. Organizing lessons, maintaining an organized class schedule, cooperating with other lecturers to organize classes, attending to students' needs and queries, preparing course material and delivering it in-class.

#### February 2023 - May 2023

#### Claims Handler Allianz Partners

Claims Handler (French) at Allianz. Duties included processing medical claims (invoice review, claim review, statements review), maintaining required targets, attending trainings and meetings, working within a team to reach common SLA goal.

#### March 2022 - February 2023

#### Platform Experience New Associate Accenture

Content Moderator (German) at Accenture for external client. Duties included maintaining a high productivity rate daily, being able to make decisions quickly and efficiently and justify them, attending weekly meetings and trainings.

#### August 2021 - present

#### External Assessor Pulse College

Seasonal freelance role for part-time audio courses. Areas taken care of include sound design for video games and audio post-production.

# **Education**

2021-2022

MA | Sound Design for Video Games
University of Chichester | ThinkSpace Education

2019-2020

**BA | Audio and Music Technology**Pulse College Dublin | Griffith College Dublin

# **Skills**

- Teamwork
- · Problem solving
- Language savvy
- Tech savvy
- · HTML, CSS, Javascript, React, Github
- · Audio DAWs (Pro Tools, Ableton)
- Microsoft Office Suite
- Google Suite

## Contact

+353892338875

Dublin, Ireland

eugeniazanna@gmail.com

https://eugenia-zanarini-portfolio.netlify.app/

linkedin.com/in/eugenia-zanarini

# Languages

- English (C2)
- Spanish (C2)
- Italian (C2)
- French (C2)
- Russian (C2)
- Ukrainian (C1)
- German (B2 C1)